<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://ttntm.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ttntm.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Responsive Web Design Certification</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/fcc-certification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/fcc-certification/</guid><description>freeCodeCamp I came across freeCodeCamp&amp;nbsp; a while ago, bookmarked it and forgot about it again. Going through my bookmarks some weeks ago, I re-discovered it and actually had a look at what they&amp;rsquo;re doing this time. As it turned out, they&amp;rsquo;ve got a huge collection of thousands of coding lessons including certifications that they&amp;rsquo;re offering for free based on donations.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t hesitate (this time) and started getting into their first course for the so called Responsive Web Design Certification.</description></item><item><title>Random Content from Data in Hugo</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/hugo-random-content-from-data/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/hugo-random-content-from-data/</guid><description>Data in Hugo Hugo comes with the possibility of storing structured content in a data file where it can be pulled from by the template placing it on the site. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen this used for things like pricing tables for example. There&amp;rsquo;s quite a bunch of use cases for random content on a website though, from customer references on a company website to quotes of the day for a literary blog.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/hello-world/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s do this I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of websites over the years, ranging from more or less official business endeavours like a small record label to more private things like a website for my wedding a while ago. I&amp;rsquo;ve never had a website just for me though, so this is something new.
Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve never been involved much with giving back to the crowd - meaning all the people posting content like reviews or code snippets online.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/about/</guid><description>About Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Tom and I work as a senior consultant for a small Austrian software development company.
We focus on corporate process management and IT documentation based on Microsoft products in conjunction with our own ISV-solutions. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of customization options in our tools so I&amp;rsquo;ve got to deal with anything from HTML, CSS and JS to SVG, XSL and VBA on a day to day basis.</description></item></channel></rss>