<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ttntm.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Microsoft Integration Stencils Pack for Visio</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/microsoft-integration-stencils-pack-visio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/microsoft-integration-stencils-pack-visio/</guid><description>Great shapes! I recently had to work on some infographics and marketing imagery for a pretty complex piece of software.
Googling up stuff like industry 4.0 or software development lifecycle infographics lead to a bunch of different &amp;ldquo;buy your image&amp;rdquo; kind of sites, going through them didn&amp;rsquo;t yield anything suitable though.
What made the whole procedure even more complicated, was the need for an SVG image. That requirement lead to the idea of doing the whole thing in Visio eventually, which is capable of producing SVGs from drawings natively.</description></item><item><title>Building a responsive menu with Tailwind CSS</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/tailwind-responsive-menu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/tailwind-responsive-menu/</guid><description>Tailwind CSS According to their docs:
Tailwind is a utility-first CSS framework for rapidly building custom user interfaces.
Being used to Bootstrap and/or other component based frameworks, this is quite a different approach.
Using Tailwind, basically everything you know from these frameworks is possible, but the way to get there is a little different. There&amp;rsquo;s no navbar, card or modal - instead, all of Tailwind&amp;rsquo;s classes can be used to actually build those components.</description></item><item><title>Using CSS Variables in Internet Explorer</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/using-css-variables-internet-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/using-css-variables-internet-explorer/</guid><description>Using CSS variables CSS variables (see: w3schools.com&amp;nbsp;) make working with stylesheets easier, no doubt about that. Defining a color, a breakpoint or even a font-family globally, makes changes easier and almost completely eliminates the copy/paste and the find/replace cycle when it comes to updates in your CSS.
Now, having to support Internet Explorer 11 and below with your CSS makes this a little less exciting, as it simply doesn&amp;rsquo;t support CSS variables at all.</description></item><item><title>Responsive Web Design Certification</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/fcc-certification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/fcc-certification/</guid><description>freeCodeCamp I came across freeCodeCamp&amp;nbsp; a while ago, bookmarked it and forgot about it again. Going through my bookmarks some weeks ago, I re-discovered it and actually had a look at what they&amp;rsquo;re doing this time. As it turned out, they&amp;rsquo;ve got a huge collection of thousands of coding lessons including certifications that they&amp;rsquo;re offering for free based on donations.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t hesitate (this time) and started getting into their first course for the so called Responsive Web Design Certification.</description></item><item><title>Random Content from Data in Hugo</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/hugo-random-content-from-data/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/hugo-random-content-from-data/</guid><description>Data in Hugo Hugo comes with the possibility of storing structured content in a data file where it can be pulled from by the template placing it on the site. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen this used for things like pricing tables for example. There&amp;rsquo;s quite a bunch of use cases for random content on a website though, from customer references on a company website to quotes of the day for a literary blog.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://ttntm.github.io/post/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ttntm.github.io/post/hello-world/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s do this I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of websites over the years, ranging from more or less official business endeavours like a small record label to more private things like a website for my wedding a while ago. I&amp;rsquo;ve never had a website just for me though, so this is something new.
Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve never been involved much with giving back to the crowd - meaning all the people posting content like reviews or code snippets online.</description></item></channel></rss>